{
  "Questions": [
    {
      "answer": "0",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_1",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Why did you get back from your trip so early?",
      "options": [
        "Because the meeting got cancel",
        "Next friday at earliest",
        "I'll be talking the train"
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "1",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_2",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Will you be attending the seminar, or do you have too much work?",
      "options": [
        "No, I will attend to it later.",
        "I will definitely attend be there.",
        "Sorry, but I didn't see it."
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "2",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_3",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Why don't you invite John to your party?",
      "options": [
        "No. he isn't.",
        "Sure, I will be there.",
        "That 's good idea"
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "1",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_4",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Could you show me where the man's sportswear section is?",
      "options": [
        "I like sport too?.",
        "Go up to the next floor?.",
        "At two o'clock?"
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "2",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_5",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "How long is the driver to tokyo from here?",
      "options": [
        "Every other week.",
        "It's great place.",
        "Roughly an hour."
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "2",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_6",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Who is going to attend the Mr. McKenzie's retirement party?",
      "options": [
        "He has not arrived yet.",
        "Let 's go right now.",
        "Everyone except Jill"
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "2",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_7",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Would you like to reserve the large hall for the event?",
      "options": [
        "Yes, I 've already completed it.",
        "It's bigger than the others.",
        "Yes, that 's good be fine."
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "0",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_8",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "The bonuses will be paid this month, don't they?",
      "options": [
        "Yes, they will.",
        "No,I paid the bill last month.",
        "Payday is this friday"
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "0",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_9",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Should I go over the material once again before showing it to the client?",
      "options": [
        "That 'd be a wise things to do",
        "He is expected to show up soon",
        "It 's about our new product"
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "2",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_10",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "What does he do for the living?",
      "options": [
        "No, he moves last week.",
        "He does it all the time.",
        "He is an accountant."
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "0",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_11",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Will you call the travel agency now or later?",
      "options": [
        "Actually, I call them yesterday.",
        "yes, I travel a lot.",
        "The flight should arrive soon."
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "0",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_12",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Don't you need this note for your presentation?",
      "options": [
        "Thanks, I almost forgot about it.",
        "Actually, there was no body present",
        "No, I didn't take note during the speech"
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "1",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_13",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Where should I put this box of ink cartridges, Mrs. Fujimot?",
      "options": [
        "At the local stationery store.",
        "Put in the next room.",
        "She is the receptionist."
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "2",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_14",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Who is good with the computers?",
      "options": [
        "Yes, It's veey good.",
        "The software come with it.",
        "John is the person you are looking for."
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "0",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_15",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Won't we have to use with overhead projector at the meeting?",
      "options": [
        "Yes, I will set it up soon.",
        "It is a big project",
        "I will head over right now"
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "2",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_16",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Where do you keep the sale report?",
      "options": [
        "Yes, I will.",
        "To the manager.",
        "In the filing cabinet."
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "1",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_17",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Do you want to proofread this proposal, or would you prefer typing up the summary?",
      "options": [
        "Thank you, that would be very nice of you.",
        "Either is okay with me.",
        "Yes, I read it over twice."
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    },
    {
      "answer": "1",
      "points": "1",
      "duration_in_seconds": "45",
      "url_audio": "listening_part2_audio_no_18",
      "negative_points": "0",
      "question": "Didn't you backup the work on computer?",
      "options": [
        "No, I came through front door.",
        "Bo, I forgot all about it",
        "I will give it back to you today"
      ],
      "question_type": "1"
    }
  ]
}